



Denver, CC



843-822-9802



hunt.kelsearyan@gmail.com



ryanhunt.github.io/Working-Portfolio-Version-2/

# Objective

My dream is to have the ability to prove my talents and drive as a web developer. I have primarily worked in a client or customer-based environment to meet immediate needs and exceed expectations. I have always been missing a creative outlet and finally feel like I have found my niche.

# KELSEA HUNT

# Experience

## February 2021-Current

Student • University of Denver Full Stack Bootcamp

## May 2017–Current

Personal Banker • Wells Fargo

### September 2017–April 2017

Benefits Administrator • Benefitfocus

# August 2012-May 2015

Office Manager • Lighthouse Tax Service

I have continuously been promoted within each company that I have had the pleasure of working for. I have been recognized with multiple awards including the Customers at the Heart Award, recognition from Atlantic Regional President for customer service and referrals at Wells Fargo and received customer health reports of 98% or higher at Benefitfocus.

#### Education

## University of Denver, Denver, Colorado

Full Stack UX/UI Program current grade A

# Trident Technical College, Charleston, South Carolina

Associates in Arts Degree

#### Communication

Ability to actively listen to either customers or coworkers in order to work toward a solution. Comprehension of what is asked of me and ability to exceed expectations.

# Leadership

Ability to give constructive feedback to other team members based on job performance as well as receiving feedback. Making decisions based on analytical thought process in a creative way. Having the technical aptitude in order to be proficient and have all available resources readily handy.

## References

References are available upon request.